[
    {
        "front": "ひゃく",
        "back": "百 \n\"100\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんびゃく",
        "back": "三百 \n\"300\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "ろっぴゃく",
        "back": "六百 \n\"600\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "せん",
        "back": "千 \n\"1000\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "にせん",
        "back": "二千 \n\"2000\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんぜん",
        "back": "三千 \n\"3000\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "まん",
        "back": "一万 \n\"10000\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちまん",
        "back": "万 \n\"10000\"",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "えん",
        "back": "円 \nYen, circle",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "よんまんえん",
        "back": "四万円 \n40,000 yen",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "とし",
        "back": "年 \nYear, age",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "にせんねん",
        "back": "二千年 \nThe year 2000",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "うえ",
        "back": "上 \nAbove, on",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "した",
        "back": "下 \nunder",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "さがる",
        "back": "下がる \nTo go down",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "じょうげ",
        "back": "上下 \nUp and down",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "なか",
        "back": "中 \nInside",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちにちじゆう",
        "back": "一日中 \nAll day (long)",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "はんとし",
        "back": "半年 \nHalf a year",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "はんぶん",
        "back": "半分 \nHalf",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "わける",
        "back": "分ける \nTo divide",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "わかる",
        "back": "分かる \nTo understand",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅっぷん",
        "back": "10 分 \n10Minutes",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゆうぶん",
        "back": "十分 \nEnough",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    },
    {
        "front": "あがる",
        "back": "上がる \nTo go up",
        "chapter": "N5 K3"
    }
]